scenepass.com 2009-12-17

# Privacy Policy at ScenePass.com

ScenePass.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: ScenePass.com Registration Forms: Our site's registration and contact forms require users to give us contact information, unique identifiers, and demographic information. Information obtained from the registration and contact forms is used to get in touch with an individual when necessary and to create membership accounts. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

**Surveys** : Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like email address), and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in. 

**Contests:**  We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information, (like email address) and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.

**External Links:  **This site contains links to other sites. ScenePass.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Venue Memberships:  **To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to our Content Manager or making corrections.

**Choice / Opt-Out:  **Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us. To opt-out, you can follow the simple instructions in the message you received upon signup.

Changes in Our Privacy Policy: Changes in our privacy policy will be posted without notice. These changes will be posted on ScenePass.com located on the Privacy Policy page.

Contacting this Web Site If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you can contact: [mail@scenepass.com](mailto:mail@scenepass.com)
